drive faster
더 빨리 운전하다
An Qiu
안 치우
Why
왜
Why only avenge my relatives?
왜 내 친척들에게만 복수합니까?
i can't even do that
난 그것조차 할 수 없어
Is it because you changed my original obsession?
내 원래 집착을 네가 바꿔서 그런 걸까?
That's why I can't move my hands
그래서 손이 안가더라구요
An Qiu
안 치우
why can't you
당신은 왜 할 수 없나요?
Break through the original obsession again?
다시 원래의 집착을 깨뜨릴까요?
You know what I hate most?
내가 제일 싫어하는 게 뭔지 알아?
Just give us hope
우리에게 희망을 주세요
Then I was disappointed again
그러다가 또 실망했어요
you betrayed my trust
넌 내 신뢰를 배신했어
betray my love
내 사랑을 배신하다
What's the difference between you and Luo Su?
당신과 Luo Su의 차이점은 무엇입니까?
You are wrong
당신은 잘못
Russell never betrayed you
러셀은 당신을 배신한 적이 없어요
I met the owner of Dreamland Club
드림랜드 클럽 주인을 만났습니다
Luo Su actually has always loved you
Luo Su는 실제로 항상 당신을 사랑했습니다
Luosu Betrays Dreamland Club
Luosu가 꿈나라를 배신하다 Club
Russell's early obsessions
러셀의 초기 집착
Be loyal to the realm of dreams
꿈의 영역에 충실하라
He's like a stubborn dog
고집 센 개 같으니라고
I couldn't even kick him out.
나는 그를 쫓아낼 수도 없었다.
It is precisely because of this
바로 이것 때문이다.
He recruited a lot of androids
그는 많은 안드로이드를 모집했습니다
I always feel
나는 항상 느낀다
There's certainly nothing wrong with the initial obsession
확실히 초기 집착에는 아무런 문제가 없습니다
Until I met Yin Tianhong
인텐홍을 만나기 전까지
Yin Tianhong took the initiative to come to the dreamland for me
Yin Tianhong이 주도적으로 나를 위해 꿈나라로 왔습니다.
Actually I don't want him to come
사실 난 그 사람이 오는 걸 원하지 않아
Can you come and tell him?
와서 그에게 말해줄 수 있나요?
let him go
그분을 석방시켜 주시 ​​오
You asked me to say that
나한테 그런 말을 해달라고 했어
This club is a charity
이 클럽은 자선단체입니다
I am
그래요
I'm not paying you less than you should.
나는 당신이 받아야 할 것보다 적은 돈을 지불하지 않습니다.
I
나
and
그리고
Who told me to stay?
누가 나한테 남으라고 했어?
You are the boss, I know you have the kindest heart
당신은 상사입니다. 나는 당신이 가장 친절한 마음을 가지고 있다는 것을 압니다.
But I couldn't resist the initial obsession
하지만 처음의 집착을 참을 수가 없었어요
Boss, do you think this is okay?
사장님, 이거 괜찮은 것 같나요?
You tell him to go
당신은 그에게 가라고 말해요
Then I will find more for you
그럼 내가 널 위해 더 찾아볼게
Better servers are coming
더 나은 서버가 오고 있습니다
I promise
약속해요
then tell me
그럼 말 해주세요
why do you want him to leave
왜 그 사람이 떠나길 바라나요?
he is a good man
그는 좋은 남자 다
depends on you
너에게 달렸다
You just hide your original obsession
원래 집착을 숨긴 채
He just tricked her into the dream world
그는 방금 그녀를 꿈의 세계로 속였습니다.
Do you think you're doing that now?
지금 그런 짓을 하고 있다고 생각하시나요?
Will he thank you?
그 사람이 고마워할까요?
He will just think you are a liar
그 사람은 당신이 거짓말쟁이라고 생각할 거예요
no problem
괜찮아요
It doesn't matter what he thinks
그 사람이 어떻게 생각하든 상관없어
He doesn't even need to know
그 사람은 알 필요조차 없어
As long as he is no longer too tired
그가 더 이상 너무 피곤하지 않은 한
Yin Tianhong is this person
인텐홍(Yin Tianhong)이 바로 이 사람이다
Accident
사고
If you are really moved,
정말 감동받았다면,
you are in danger
당신은 위험에 처해 있습니다
I won't help you open this mouth
난 네가 이 입을 여는 것을 돕지 않을 거야
Does he want to stay?
그는 머물고 싶어합니까?
That's his own business
그건 그 사람의 일이에요
I don’t know if Luo Su was initially obsessed with this.
Luo Su가 처음에 이것에 집착했는지는 모르겠습니다.
Still trapped by my own heart
아직도 내 마음에 갇혀있어
He took the initiative to let Yin Tianhong go
그는 Yin Tianhong을 보내기 위해 주도권을 잡았습니다.
He actually set a trap to stimulate it
실제로 자극을 주기 위해 함정을 설치한 거죠
I'm just kidding you
농담이에요
let you go now
이제 널 보내줘
Never go back to dreamland again
다시는 꿈나라로 돌아가지 마세요
You said you killed the robot
로봇을 죽였다고 하더군요
It’s to release their original obsession
원래 집착을 풀어주는 거다.
But Russell never
하지만 러셀은 결코
Imprisoned by his true obsession
진정한 집착에 사로잡혀
He sets a trap for you to leave the dreamland
그는 당신이 꿈나라를 떠나도록 함정을 놓는다
He's always protecting you, you know?
그 사람은 항상 당신을 보호하고 있어요. 아시죠?
you are talking nonsense
넌 말도 안되는 소리를 하고 있어
He obviously did it out of initial obsession
그 사람은 분명히 처음에 집착해서 그런 짓을 한 게 분명해요
betray me
나를 배신하다
I can see that you are very stubborn.
나는 당신이 매우 완고하다는 것을 알 수 있습니다.
You can never truly trust others
당신은 결코 다른 사람을 진심으로 믿을 수 없다
if not
그렇지 않다면
How could you be deceived by Luo Su so easily?
어떻게 그렇게 쉽게 Luo Su에게 속을 수 있었나요?
How could you not know that he wanted to save you?
그가 당신을 구하고 싶어한다는 것을 어떻게 모를 수 있겠습니까?
Have you said enough?
충분히 말했는가?
you think you are god
당신은 당신이 신이라고 생각합니까?
In fact, you are just a coward with low self-esteem.
사실 당신은 자존감이 낮은 겁쟁이일 뿐입니다.
Even you underestimate yourself
당신조차 자신을 과소평가하고 있어요
I didn't, I didn't
난 안 그랬어, 안 그랬어
Then why don't you dare to kill someone?
그렇다면 감히 사람을 죽이지 못하는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Is this the lowest cost to shut down android?
이것이 Android를 종료하는 데 드는 가장 저렴한 비용입니까?
Yin Tianhong
인 티안훙
I'm not a person who dares not face myself
나는 감히 나 자신과 마주하지 못하는 사람이 아니다.
that is you
그건 너야
Cheng Nuo
쳉 누오
You have no right to say this to him.
당신은 그 사람에게 이런 말을 할 권리가 없습니다.
Yin Tianhong
인 티안훙
calm
침착한
Why
왜
Why is he still lying to me?
그 사람은 왜 아직도 나에게 거짓말을 하는 걸까?
because he loves you
그 사람이 당신을 사랑하기 때문에
That's why he wants to save you
그래서 그 사람은 당신을 구하고 싶어하는 거예요
I know you love him too
너도 그 사람을 사랑하는 걸 알아
That's why you're in so much pain right now
그래서 지금 너무 괴로워하는 거야
halo
후광
Halo Zhou Qi
헤일로 저우 치
Wan Guofeng
완궈펑
The suspect has taken hostages
용의자는 인질을 잡았다
It doesn't matter if he's a robot or not.
그가 로봇인지 아닌지는 중요하지 않습니다.
handle all of this
이 모든 걸 처리해
I want to trouble you now
지금 당신을 괴롭히고 싶어요
Cooperate with external work
대외업무에 협력
Now we take over here
이제 우리가 여기를 맡는다
Clear
분명한
Do you still remember our agreement?
아직도 우리의 합의를 기억하고 있나요?
we'll leave here together
우리는 여기서 함께 떠날 거야
leave
떠나다
lay down your weapons
무기를 내려놔
An Qiu
안 치우
leave
떠나다
calm
침착한
direct
직접
This world cannot tolerate us
이 세상은 우리를 용납할 수 없어
accustomed to
에 익숙해
Don't shoot
쏘지 마세요
He has hostages
그에게는 인질이 있다
please leave
떠나주세요
I said don't shoot
쏘지 말라고 했는데
Yin Tianhong
인 티안훙
Can you put the knife down?
칼을 내려놓을 수 있나요?
An Qiu
안 치우
you don't have to keep living
계속 살 필요는 없어
Bear the pain of being deceived
속은 것의 고통을 참아라
Yin Tianhong, stop being stubborn.
Yin Tianhong, 고집을 부리지 마세요.
Let me help you, okay?
내가 도와줄게, 알았지?
Yin Tianhong
인 티안훙
You can't make decisions for me
당신은 나를 위해 결정을 내릴 수 없습니다
i will accompany you
내가 너와 동행할게
Yin Tianhong is dead
인텐홍은 죽었어
It's because of hatred
증오 때문이에요
also because of love
그것도 사랑 때문에
Maybe he's been confused
어쩌면 그 사람은 혼란스러워했을지도 몰라
because he doesn't know
그 사람은 모르니까
my highest emotion
내 최고의 감정
what on earth is that
도대체 그게 뭐야?
So he only felt pain
그래서 그 사람은 고통만 느꼈지
He can't realize it either
그 사람도 그걸 깨닫지 못하고
The image that has always been etched in his mind
늘 마음속에 각인되어 있던 이미지
symbolic
상징적인
In fact, this is life and hope
사실 이것이 삶이고 희망이다
Cheng Nuo, how are you?
쳉 누오(Cheng Nuo), 잘 지내요?
Di mana An Qiu?
디 마나 안 치우?
in the waiting room
대기실에서
An Qiu
안 치우
sorry
죄송합니다
But it's dangerous for you to stay here
하지만 여기 있으면 위험해
They will definitely say that
그 사람들은 분명 그렇게 말할 거예요.
Hide your identity and walk into bright eyes
정체를 숨기고 빛나는 눈 속으로 걸어들어가
Then I'll take this opportunity to punish you.
그렇다면 이번 기회에 당신을 처벌하겠습니다.
continue
계속하다
you must go with me
너는 나와 함께 가야 해
I will definitely find a way to save you
반드시 널 구할 방법을 찾을 거야
I won't go with you
나는 당신과 함께 가지 않을 것입니다
An Qiu
안 치우
Do not do
하지 마세요
i would rather be punished
차라리 처벌을 받겠다
I no longer want to be a tool dependent on the pity of others.
나는 더 이상 타인의 연민에 의존하는 도구가 되고 싶지 않습니다.
I know you hate Mingmou
네가 밍무를 싫어하는 거 알아
He hates me more and more
그 사람이 날 점점 더 미워해
But can you give up on yourself?
하지만 당신은 자신을 포기할 수 있습니까?
There is still hope
아직 희망은 있다
You hope that I will continue to work hard and succeed.
계속해서 열심히 일하고 성공하기를 바랍니다.
failed experiment
실패한 실험
Or those who harm their own kind?
아니면 동족에게 해를 끼치는 자입니까?
An Qiu
안 치우
you're right
네가 옳아
I hate you
당신이 싫어요
But I hate myself even more
하지만 난 내가 더 싫어
hate myself for being weak
약한 내가 싫어
fail
실패하다
I hate fate too
나도 운명은 싫어
Please introduce yourself
자기 소개 부탁드립니다
An Qiu, I'm sorry
안 치우, 미안해
let me beg you
부탁할게
leave here
여기를 떠나
don't let me see you again
다시는 볼 수 없게 해줘
Can you please not take An Qiu away?
An Qiu를 데려가실 수 없나요?
I beg you
부탁드립니다
An Qiu asked you to come
안 치우가 오라고 했어요
No
아니요
He doesn't need my help
그 사람은 내 도움이 필요하지 않아
Then why do you insist on saving him?
그렇다면 왜 그를 구하겠다고 고집하는 걸까요?
Although An Qiu is a bionic person,
안추(An Qiu)는 생체 공학적 인간이지만,
But he is no different from us
하지만 그 사람도 우리와 다르지 않아
I know
알아요
An Qiu's situation is very miserable
안추의 상황은 매우 비참하다
But he is a robot and we have bright eyes
하지만 그는 로봇이고 우리는 눈이 밝습니다
we have our responsibilities
우리에게는 책임이 있다
In this case, do we have no other choice?
이런 경우에는 다른 선택의 여지가 없나요?
I can't do anything now
난 지금 아무것도 할 수 없어
Do you know how many pairs of eyes there are out there?
세상에 눈이 몇 쌍이나 있는지 아시나요?
Are you watching us?
우리를 보고 있나요?
Something big happened last night
어젯밤에 큰 일이 일어났어
Everyone knows An Qiu’s identity
모두가 안추의 정체를 알고 있다
if no action is taken
아무 조치도 취하지 않으면
So how should we give an explanation to the outside world?
그러면 외부 세계에 어떻게 설명해야 할까요?
minister
장관
An Qiu comes from my mother's laboratory
An Qiu는 어머니의 실험실에서 왔습니다.
Bionic research objects
생체 공학 연구 개체
My mother's death may have something to do with him
우리 엄마의 죽음이 그 사람과 관련이 있을 수도 있어
if he is fired
만약 그가 해고된다면
The truth about my mother's death
어머니의 죽음에 관한 진실
It could be lost forever.
영원히 잃어버릴 수도 있습니다.
So please
그러니 제발
even for my mother
엄마를 위해서라도
You don't want him to die in an unknown way, right?
그 사람이 알 수 없는 방식으로 죽는 걸 원하지 않겠죠?
There is currently no evidence of this
현재 이에 대한 증거는 없습니다
An Qiu is related to your mother's case
An Qiu는 당신 어머니의 사건과 관련이 있습니다
If you can connect two things together
두 가지를 하나로 연결할 수 있다면
perhaps
아마도
we can defer disposal
우리는 폐기를 연기할 수 있습니다
give me some more time
나에게 좀 더 시간을 줘
I will definitely find it
반드시 찾아낼 거야
halo
후광
I am Wan Guofeng
나는 완궈펑입니다
There are still doubts about the Anqiu case.
안추 사건에 대해서는 여전히 의구심이 남아 있다.
Need clarification
설명이 필요함
see if you can
당신이 할 수 있는지 확인
postpone it for a few more days
며칠 더 미루세요
Understood
이해했다
Your mother and I are old classmates
네 엄마와 나는 오랜 동창이야
He said before that he wanted to rent this place from me
그 사람은 전에 나한테서 이곳을 빌려주고 싶다고 말했어
research
연구
There was always a girl by his side at that time
그 때 그 옆에는 항상 여자가 있었어
It turned out to be Anqiu
Anqiu로 밝혀졌습니다
Are they just the two of them?
그 둘뿐인가요?
of
~의
It seems that the two chat frequently.
두 사람은 자주 대화를 나누는 것 같다.
I think we get along well
내 생각에 우리는 잘 지내고 있는 것 같아
after
~ 후에
Your mother also introduced him to our internship.
당신 어머니도 그에게 우리 인턴십을 소개해 주셨지요.
Strong working ability and good performance
강력한 작업 능력과 좋은 성능
everything is here
모든 것이 여기에 있습니다
We haven't moved yet
우리는 아직 이사하지 않았습니다
Take the time to see for yourself
직접 살펴보는 시간을 가져보세요
The first time was June 5th
첫 번째는 6월 5일이었습니다.
Halo Anqing
헤일로 안칭
I am Zhang Ye
나는 장예입니다
people engaged in psychological research
심리학 연구에 종사하는 사람들
Nice to meet you
만나서 반가워요
How do you get a good rest?
좋은 휴식을 취하는 방법은 무엇입니까?
I see your skin is slowly recovering.
피부가 서서히 회복되고 있는 걸 보니
why am i here
내가 왜 여기 있지?
What's left
남은 것
he is there
그는 거기 있다
The purpose of our experiment is
우리 실험의 목적은
Get over your initial obsession with Android
Android에 대한 초기 집착을 극복하세요
and psychological counseling
그리고 심리상담
Then I chose you
그럼 난 당신을 선택했어요
I hope we can work together
우리가 함께 일할 수 있기를 바랍니다
why me
왜 나야
Why did you ask me out alone?
왜 나한테 혼자 데이트 신청한 거야?
perhaps
아마도
Your initial obsession has failed
당신의 초기 집착은 실패했습니다
Of course this is just my guess
물론 이건 내 추측일 뿐이야
Don't worry, I won't force you
걱정하지 마세요, 강요하진 않을 거예요
Take a good rest first
우선 푹 쉬세요
do what you want
원하는 대로 하세요
if you need anything you can tell me
필요한 게 있으면 나한테 말해도 돼
Then let's go here first today
그럼 오늘은 먼저 여기로 갑시다
Thanks
감사해요
It's over the first time
처음으로 끝났어
To avoid unnecessary problems
불필요한 문제를 피하기 위해
Can I call you Anqiu from now on?
이제부터 안추라고 불러도 될까요?
During this process
이 과정에서
I may have to ask you a lot of questions
질문을 많이 해야 할 것 같아요
You may also receive some medications
일부 약물을 투여받을 수도 있습니다.
if you don't want to do this
당신이 이것을하고 싶지 않다면
you can reject me anytime
넌 언제든지 나를 거절할 수 있어
it's definitely my fault
확실히 내 잘못이야
the only thing you have to do
당신이 해야 할 유일한 일은
stay true to yourself
항상 진실하라
An Qiu
안 치우
Are you OK
괜찮으세요
minister
장관
why are you here
당신은 왜 여기에 있습니까?
I finally found you
드디어 당신을 찾았어요
you are that person
당신이 그 사람이에요
Zhang Ya’s hidden bionic man
장야(Zhang Ya)의 숨겨진 생체 공학 맨
Do you know Zhang Ya?
장야를 아시나요?
An idea to break away from the initial obsession with android
안드로이드에 대한 초기 집착에서 벗어나기 위한 아이디어
He was the one who made the suggestion
제안을 한 사람이 바로 그 사람이에요.
Although I am working in Mingmou
나는 Mingmou에서 일하고 있지만
But over the years
하지만 수년에 걸쳐
I think humans are cruel to robots
인간은 로봇에게 잔인하다고 생각해요
In fact, robots and humans
사실 로봇과 인간은
no difference
차이 없음
What is your relationship with Ming?
밍이랑 무슨 관계야?
It should be said that we have a cooperative relationship
협력관계라고 해야되나
We do a lot of things with android
우리는 안드로이드로 많은 일을 합니다.
A very important psychological experiment
매우 중요한 심리학 실험
so
그래서
When Zhang Ya proposed this plan to me,
Zhang Ya가 나에게 이 계획을 제안했을 때,
I think this is a turning point
이번이 전환점인 것 같아요
If the original obsession could be replaced
원래의 집착을 바꿀 수 있다면
even removed
심지어 제거됨
This will help you better integrate into society
이는 사회에 더 잘 통합되는 데 도움이 될 것입니다
live well
잘 살다
able
할 수 있는
Are you living your life on your own terms?
당신은 자신의 방식대로 인생을 살고 있습니까?
certainly
틀림없이
Humans are the ones who created us
인간은 우리를 창조한 존재이다
It is also humans who destroy us
우리를 파괴하는 것도 인간이다
What is being saved now is humanity.
지금 구원받고 있는 것은 인류이다.
If a mother
어머니라면
He doesn't love his children at all
그는 그의 아이들을 전혀 사랑하지 않는다
Then why did she give birth to him?
그렇다면 그녀는 왜 그를 낳았습니까?
at first i thought
처음에 나는 생각했다
we have the same goal
우리는 같은 목표를 가지고 있어요
But as the experiment progresses
하지만 실험이 진행되면서
I feel like the gap between us is getting bigger and bigger
우리 사이의 간격이 점점 더 벌어지는 것 같아
Zhang Ya told me she found it
Zhang Ya가 찾았다고 말했어요
perfect test subject
완벽한 시험과목
I asked him who he was, but he wouldn't tell me.
나는 그에게 그가 누구인지 물었지만 그는 나에게 말해주지 않았습니다.
I've felt it ever since
예전부터 느껴왔어
He has other plans
그 사람은 다른 계획이 있어
My current relationship with my children
현재 나와 아이들의 관계
not too good
너무 좋지 않아
Then I have no choice
그렇다면 나에겐 선택의 여지가 없다
no way to communicate
의사소통할 방법이 없어
yes
예
Relationship with Cheng Nuo
쳉누오와의 관계
this is always bad
이건 항상 나쁘다
He wants to change his initial obsession with robots
그는 로봇에 대한 초기 집착을 바꾸고 싶어합니다.
Let them become researchers
연구자가 되도록 해주세요
at first i thought
처음에 나는 생각했다
This is what scientists insist on
과학자들이 주장하는 것이 바로 이것이다.
But then I found out
그런데 그러다가 알게 됐어요
This is his confession to his son
아들에게 한 고백이다.
maybe because i don't know
어쩌면 내가 모르기 때문에
How to express your love for each other
서로에 대한 사랑을 표현하는 방법
maybe we missed it
어쩌면 우리가 놓쳤을지도 몰라
ability to love
사랑하는 능력
That
저것
That's just because you're human
그건 바로 당신이 인간이기 때문이에요
my early obsession
나의 초기 집착
This is to protect your family and the family that loves you
이는 당신의 가족과 당신을 사랑하는 가족을 보호하기 위한 것입니다.
So after Anyang died
그래서 안양이 죽은 뒤
I don't even know who to love anymore
이제 누구를 사랑해야 할지 모르겠어
I don’t even have the original obsession
원래 집착도 없어
If it is Android
안드로이드라면
Not even his initial obsession.
그의 초기 집착도 아닙니다.
What is the meaning of my life?
내 삶의 의미는 무엇입니까?
An Qiu
안 치우
What I want to tell you is
제가 말씀드리고 싶은 것은
Our sorrow is justified
우리의 슬픔은 정당하다
we have the right to grieve
우리는 슬퍼할 권리가 있다
Even if you lose your original obsession
원래의 집착을 잃어도
We can still find a way out together
우리는 여전히 함께 탈출구를 찾을 수 있습니다
So he wants to do it
그래서 그 사람이 하고 싶어하는 거야
You can stay with Cheng Nuo
Cheng Nuo와 함께 머물 수 있습니다
obey him completely and protect his people
그에게 온전히 순종하고 그의 백성을 보호하소서
when needed
필요할 때
can sacrifice for him
그를 위해 희생할 수 있다
scissors, paper, rock
가위, 종이, 바위
We played chess until late last night
우리는 어젯밤 늦게까지 체스를 두었어요
I do not remember
기억이 안나요
Recently taken reagents
최근 복용한 시약
Do you feel sick?
너 아프니?
I've been dreaming about it lately
최근에 꿈을 꾸었어요
I have a brother
나는 형제가있다
But this dream is getting blurry
하지만 점점 흐려지는 꿈
I dreamed that we lived in the same room
같은 방에 사는 꿈을 꿨어
in an abandoned house
버려진 집에서
Living conditions are very difficult
생활여건이 매우 어렵습니다
but very happy
하지만 매우 행복해요
He did it
그가 해냈어
He protected his murderous son very well.
그는 살인한 아들을 아주 잘 보호했습니다.
he seems to have done it
그 사람이 해낸 것 같아
Tapi An Qiu
타피 안 치우
We still have a chance to change this
우리에겐 아직 이것을 바꿀 수 있는 기회가 있습니다
Your initial obsession has changed
당신의 초기 집착이 바뀌었습니다
This is a fact
이건 사실이다
but in you
하지만 당신 안에는
Have neurons that can save other robots
다른 로봇을 구할 수 있는 뉴런 보유
but I
하지만 나는
Is there any way to extract it for you?
그것을 추출할 수 있는 방법이 있나요?
Sorry to ask you suddenly
갑자기 물어봐서 미안해
Is there anything wrong with the previous experiment?
이전 실험에 문제가 있나요?
it has nothing to do with you
너랑은 아무 상관 없어
This is between me and my partner
이건 나와 내 파트너 사이의 문제야
I'm afraid he wants
그 사람이 원하는 것 같아 유감이네요
Tips for getting rid of initial distress
초기 고통을 없애기 위한 팁
suitable for humans
인간에게 적합
He wants to control human emotions
그는 인간의 감정을 통제하고 싶어한다
you want
당신이 원하는
Do you still believe in humans?
아직도 인간을 믿으시나요?
He wants to extract the neurons in your body
그는 당신 몸의 뉴런을 추출하고 싶어합니다
create an android
안드로이드를 만들어라
Pandora's box has been opened
판도라의 상자가 열렸다
I won't allow him to open a second one
나는 그 사람이 두 번째 것을 열도록 허용하지 않을 것입니다
What can I do for you?
내가 당신을 위해 무엇을 할 수?
you don't need to do anything
당신은 아무것도 할 필요가 없습니다
This is your last injection
이게 마지막 주사야
I might increase the dose
복용량을 늘릴 수도 있어요
The goal is to protect you
목표는 당신을 보호하는 것입니다
When you wake up you might forget who I am
자고 일어나면 내가 누군지 잊어버릴지도 몰라
You will lose your previous memories
이전 기억을 잃게 됩니다.
But it doesn't matter
하지만 그건 중요하지 않아요
I will prepare background information for you
나는 당신을 위해 배경 정보를 준비할 것입니다
and where you work and study
그리고 당신이 일하고 공부하는 곳
You also forget that you are a robot
당신도 로봇이라는 사실을 잊어버렸어요
Wait until you open your eyes again
다시 눈을 뜰 때까지 기다려
This is the new you
이것이 바로 새로운 당신이다
I do not want to forget you
나는 당신을 잊고 싶지 않아요
Even if you forget me
나를 잊어도
I also know you will become one of them
너도 그 중 하나가 될 걸 나도 알아
Very very good psychiatrist
아주 아주 좋은 정신과 의사
I won't tell him everything about you
나는 그에게 당신에 관한 모든 것을 말하지 않을 것입니다